A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 6 FA1326
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 6
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. Busby-Whitehead (2004-0321), 2004-2007 (Box 504, Folder 3781-3782)
  - University of Pittsburgh: N. Resnick (2004-0212), 2004-2007 (Box 504, Folder 3783)
  - University of Pittsburgh: C. Reynolds III (2004-0334), 2004-2007 (Box 505, Folder 3784)
  - Indiana University: S. Counsell (2004-0323), 2004-2007 (Box 505, Folder 3785)
  - University of California, San Diego: D. Jeste (2004-0338), 2004-2007 (Box 505, Folder 3786-3787)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2005-0060), 2005-2007 (Box 505, Folder 3788)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: R. Leipzig (2005-0058), 2005-2007 (Box 505, Folder 3789)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: R. Leipzig (2006-0098), 2006-2011 (Box 506, Folder 3790-3791)
  - Boston Medical Center: R. Silliman (2006-0167), 2006-2010 (Box 506, Folder 3792-3793)
  - Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center: L. Lipsitz (2006-0077), 2006-2011 (Box 506, Folder 3794-3795)
  - University of Utah: M. Supiano (2006-0052), 2006-2008 (Box 506, Folder 3796)
  - Duke University: H. Cohen (2006-0109), 2006-2011 (Box 507, Folder 3797-3798)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: G. Taffet (2006-0166), 2006-2011 (Box 507, Folder 3799-3800)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2006-0079), 2006-2011 (Box 507, Folder 3801-3802)
  - University of Pennsylvania: J. Johnson (2006-0170), 2006-2011 (Box 507, Folder 3803)
  - University of California, San Francisco: C. Landefeld (2006-0108), 2006-2011 (Box 508, Folder 3804-3806)
  - University of Colorado: R. Schwartz (2006-0169), 2006-2011 (Box 508, Folder 3807)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (2006-0082), 2006-2011 (Box 508, Folder 3808-3809)
  - University of California, San Diego: D. Jeste (2007-0287), 2007-2011 (Box 508, Folder 3810)
  - Rhode Island Hospital: R. Besdine (2007-0097), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3811)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2007-0009), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3812)
  - Wake Forest University: J. Williamson (2007-0123), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3813)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2007-0006), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3814)
  - University of Wisconsin: S. Asthana (2007-0121), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3815)
  - University of Pittsburgh: N. Resnick (2007-0007), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3816)
  - University of Pittsburgh: C. Reynolds III (2007-0285), 2007-2011 (Box 509, Folder 3817)
  - Cornell University: M. Reid (2008-0141), 2008-2011 (Box 510, Folder 3818)
  - Indiana University: S. Counsell (2008-0144), 2008-2011 (Box 510, Folder 3819)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. Busby-Whitehead (2008-0145), 2008-2011 (Box 510, Folder 3820)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (2008-0146), 2008-2011 (Box 510, Folder 3821)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence: T. Johnson (2008-142), 2008-2011 (Box 510, Folder 3822)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Unutzer (98-297), 1998-2005 (Box 510, Folder 3823-3824)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Unutzer (98-297), 1998-2005 (Box 511, Folder 3825-3826)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Unutzer (98-302), 1998-2005 (Box 511, Folder 3827-3830)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Unutzer (2000-0183), 2000-2005 (Box 511, Folder 3831)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Unutzer (2000-0183), 2000-2005 (Box 512, Folder 3832)
  - University of Washington: J. Unutzer (2004-001), 2004-2012 (Box 512, Folder 3833-3837)
  - University of Washington: J. Unutzer (2004-001), 2004-2012 (Box 513, Folder 3838-3844)
  - University of Washington: J. Unutzer (2004-001), 2004-2012 (Box 514, Folder 3845-3846)
  - Kaiser Permante: R. Della Penna (96-202, declined), 1996 (Box 514, Folder 3847-3849)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (96-204, declined), 1996 (Box 515, Folder 3850)
  - Harvard: S. Churchill (96-206, declined), 1996 (Box 515, Folder 3851-3852)
  - University of North Carolina: M. Williams (96-208, declined), 1996 (Box 515, Folder 3853-3854)
  - University of Minnesota School of Nursing: M. Bull (91-227, declined), 1991 (Box 516, Folder 3855)
  - University of Pennsylvania School of Nursing: C. Fagan (91-276, declined), 1991 (Box 516, Folder 3856)
  - University Hospitals of Cleveland: R. Fortinsky (96-342, declined), 1996 (Box 516, Folder 3857)
  - University of Southern California: E. Schneider (no grant number, declined), 1996 (Box 516, Folder 3858)
  - Center for the Study of Services: R. Krughoff (89-308, withdrawn), 1989 (Box 516, Folder 3859)
  - American Lung Association of New York: G. Caron (96-230, withdrawn), 1996 (Box 516, Folder 3860)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2001-0115), 2001-2005 (Box 516, Folder 3861-3864)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2001-0115), 2001-2005 (Box 517, Folder 3865-3869)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2001-0115), 2001-2005 (Box 518, Folder 3870-3872)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2004-0003), 2004-2009 (Box 518, Folder 3873-3875)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2004-0003), 2004-2009 (Box 519, Folder 3876-3882)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2004-0003) Separated media: 2015:065:001 - "AACN Curriculum Evaluation Report", 2006 August; 2 CD-Rs (Box 2015:065:001, Folder 3879)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please consult a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) in Nursing: The Measurement Group: G. Huba (2004-0003), 2004-2009 (Box 520, Folder 3883-3887)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): Communications and Dissemination Initiative: J. Beilenson (2005-0295), 2005-2009 (Box 520, Folder 3888)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): Communications and Dissemination Initiative: J. Beilenson (2005-0295), 2005-2009 (Box 521, Folder 3889-3890)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): Communications and Dissemination Initiative: J. Beilenson (2008-0127), 2008-2012 (Box 521, Folder 3891-3893)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): 75th Anniversary Commemoration: C. Rieder (2002-0283), 2002-2006 (Box 521, Folder 3894-3896)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): Generalist Physician Model: D. Regenstreif (92-320), 1992-1994 (Box 522, Folder 3897-3899)
  - RAND Corporation: H. Pincus (2001-349), 2001-2005 (Box 522, Folder 3900)
    - RAND Corporation: H. Pincus (2001-349) Separated media: 2015:065:002 - "Changing the Trajectory of Serious and Chronic Illness in Older Adults", 2005 June 2; 5 DVDs (Box T1, Dvd v16)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructions.
  - Unsorted Grant Publications, 2000s (Box 522, Folder 3901-3902)
  - 2015:065:003 - Society of Hospital Medicine Geriatrics Task Force: Clinical Toolbox for Geriatric Care, 2004; 1 CD-ROM (Box 2015:065:003, Folder 3902)
  - 2015:065:004 - Hartford GeroRich Project Evaluation Tools and materials from 2003 Regional meeting Resource Fair, 1 CD-R (Box 2015:065:004, Folder 3902)
  - 2005:065:005 - CSWE SAGE-SW Faculty Development Institute, undated; 1 CD-R (Box 2015:065:005, Folder 3902)
  - Card Index of Grantees, 1969-1977; Index cards (Box 523, Folder 3903)